
> test
> npm run test:security:unit


> test:security:unit
> tsx --test tests/*.test.ts

TAP version 13
# Subtest: email selection is literal, normalized and not a wildcard
ok 1 - email selection is literal, normalized and not a wildcard
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.2505
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: ambiguity across pages and lookup failures prevent admin promotion
ok 2 - ambiguity across pages and lookup failures prevent admin promotion
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.1174
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: admin saves explicit token, API response never contains credential
ok 3 - admin saves explicit token, API response never contains credential
  ---
  duration_ms: 67.5223
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: normal user is denied before reading or modifying payment secrets
ok 4 - normal user is denied before reading or modifying payment secrets
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.38
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: empty token preserves existing token; only explicit new value replaces it
ok 5 - empty token preserves existing token; only explicit new value replaces it
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.4208
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: missing token prevents activation and persistence; raw errors are sanitized
ok 6 - missing token prevents activation and persistence; raw errors are sanitized
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.6865
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: disabled config rejects environment fallback; active without token rejects charge
ok 7 - disabled config rejects environment fallback; active without token rejects charge
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.7353
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: webhook missing secret never invokes payment processing or exposes details
ok 8 - webhook missing secret never invokes payment processing or exposes details
  ---
  duration_ms: 75.014
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: public callback origin requires HTTPS and explicit allowlist membership
ok 9 - public callback origin requires HTTPS and explicit allowlist membership
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.4887
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: demo examples keep existing values and calculations reference newly inserted IDs
ok 10 - demo examples keep existing values and calculations reference newly inserted IDs
  ---
  duration_ms: 8.8749
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: creation, demo seed and removal propagate errors without fallback writes or false success
ok 11 - creation, demo seed and removal propagate errors without fallback writes or false success
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.8777
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: license extension retries a conflicting grant instead of losing it
ok 12 - license extension retries a conflicting grant instead of losing it
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.5089
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: license preserves calendar month overflow and trial exact-day arithmetic
ok 13 - license preserves calendar month overflow and trial exact-day arithmetic
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.6025
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: unknown commit outcome is never automatically replayed
ok 14 - unknown commit outcome is never automatically replayed
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.2084
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: conflict retries are bounded and never report false success
ok 15 - conflict retries are bounded and never report false success
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.9555
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: database text item type is validated without inventing an enum
ok 16 - database text item type is validated without inventing an enum
  ---
  duration_ms: 8.4691
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: product stock remains numeric; services persist null in forms, duplication and demo
ok 17 - product stock remains numeric; services persist null in forms, duplication and demo
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.293
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: Mercado Pago insert explicitly supplies provider and pending state
ok 18 - Mercado Pago insert explicitly supplies provider and pending state
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.635
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: payment verification refuses another provider, missing charge and amount mismatch
ok 19 - payment verification refuses another provider, missing charge and amount mismatch
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.4876
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: signup is closed for absent, null or disabled configuration; explicit true enables it
ok 20 - signup is closed for absent, null or disabled configuration; explicit true enables it
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.3391
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: trial uses persisted backend expiration, otherwise creation plus 30 days without writes
ok 21 - trial uses persisted backend expiration, otherwise creation plus 30 days without writes
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.6633
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: accepts a valid recent signature with current or previous secret
ok 22 - accepts a valid recent signature with current or previous secret
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.8102
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: rejects an otherwise valid old signature
ok 23 - rejects an otherwise valid old signature
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.6495
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: rejects an invalid signature
ok 24 - rejects an invalid signature
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.6768
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: does not mix sandbox and production payments
ok 25 - does not mix sandbox and production payments
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.3138
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: classifies payment states conservatively
ok 26 - classifies payment states conservatively
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.3144
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: GET, invalid signatures, stale/future timestamps and ambiguous ids never process
ok 27 - GET, invalid signatures, stale/future timestamps and ambiguous ids never process
  ---
  duration_ms: 68.1722
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: valid notifications use only signed id and repeat through the idempotent processor
ok 28 - valid notifications use only signed id and repeat through the idempotent processor
  ---
  duration_ms: 5.1
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: missing configuration and processor failures produce retryable errors
ok 29 - missing configuration and processor failures produce retryable errors
  ---
  duration_ms: 9.9278
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: disabled or missing payment configuration blocks new charges even with env token
ok 30 - disabled or missing payment configuration blocks new charges even with env token
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.4811
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: existing payments can still be reconciled and active charges use credential fallback
ok 31 - existing payments can still be reconciled and active charges use credential fallback
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.2574
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: promotional discount rejects out-of-range and non-finite values
ok 32 - promotional discount rejects out-of-range and non-finite values
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.3599
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: discount boundaries produce a non-negative price and expose loss
ok 33 - discount boundaries produce a non-negative price and expose loss
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.7233
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: minimum mode ignores unused profit and discount, including NaN
ok 34 - minimum mode ignores unused profit and discount, including NaN
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.8119
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: allocation requires positive sales or an explicitly supplied manual amount
ok 35 - allocation requires positive sales or an explicitly supplied manual amount
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.7446
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: non-finite costs and invalid installments cannot be saved as valid calculations
ok 36 - non-finite costs and invalid installments cannot be saved as valid calculations
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.4757
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: checkout URL follows the configured Mercado Pago environment
ok 37 - checkout URL follows the configured Mercado Pago environment
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.0645
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..37
# tests 37
# suites 0
# pass 37
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 2023.2502
