
> test:security
> npm run test:security:unit


> test:security:unit
> tsx --test tests/*.test.ts

TAP version 13
# Subtest: email selection is literal, normalized and not a wildcard
ok 1 - email selection is literal, normalized and not a wildcard
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.1115
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: ambiguity across pages and lookup failures prevent admin promotion
ok 2 - ambiguity across pages and lookup failures prevent admin promotion
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.1037
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: demo examples keep existing values and calculations reference newly inserted IDs
ok 3 - demo examples keep existing values and calculations reference newly inserted IDs
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.2266
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: creation, demo seed and removal propagate errors without fallback writes or false success
ok 4 - creation, demo seed and removal propagate errors without fallback writes or false success
  ---
  duration_ms: 5.9215
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: database text item type is validated without inventing an enum
ok 5 - database text item type is validated without inventing an enum
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.0872
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: product stock remains numeric; services persist null in forms, duplication and demo
ok 6 - product stock remains numeric; services persist null in forms, duplication and demo
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.9596
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: Mercado Pago insert explicitly supplies provider and pending state
ok 7 - Mercado Pago insert explicitly supplies provider and pending state
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.5372
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: payment verification refuses another provider, missing charge and amount mismatch
ok 8 - payment verification refuses another provider, missing charge and amount mismatch
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.3588
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: signup is closed for absent, null or disabled configuration; explicit true enables it
ok 9 - signup is closed for absent, null or disabled configuration; explicit true enables it
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.3178
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: trial uses persisted backend expiration, otherwise creation plus 30 days without writes
ok 10 - trial uses persisted backend expiration, otherwise creation plus 30 days without writes
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.7094
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: accepts a valid recent signature with current or previous secret
ok 11 - accepts a valid recent signature with current or previous secret
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.9802
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: rejects an otherwise valid old signature
ok 12 - rejects an otherwise valid old signature
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.6644
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: rejects an invalid signature
ok 13 - rejects an invalid signature
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.7092
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: does not mix sandbox and production payments
ok 14 - does not mix sandbox and production payments
  ---
  duration_ms: 14.4596
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: classifies payment states conservatively
ok 15 - classifies payment states conservatively
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.4632
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: GET, invalid signatures, stale/future timestamps and ambiguous ids never process
ok 16 - GET, invalid signatures, stale/future timestamps and ambiguous ids never process
  ---
  duration_ms: 47.9327
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: valid notifications use only signed id and repeat through the idempotent processor
ok 17 - valid notifications use only signed id and repeat through the idempotent processor
  ---
  duration_ms: 4.6499
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: missing configuration and processor failures produce retryable errors
ok 18 - missing configuration and processor failures produce retryable errors
  ---
  duration_ms: 6.2875
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: disabled or missing payment configuration blocks new charges even with env token
ok 19 - disabled or missing payment configuration blocks new charges even with env token
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.8074
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: existing payments can still be reconciled and active charges use credential fallback
ok 20 - existing payments can still be reconciled and active charges use credential fallback
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.3103
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: promotional discount rejects out-of-range and non-finite values
ok 21 - promotional discount rejects out-of-range and non-finite values
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.8426
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: discount boundaries produce a non-negative price and expose loss
ok 22 - discount boundaries produce a non-negative price and expose loss
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.738
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: minimum mode ignores unused profit and discount, including NaN
ok 23 - minimum mode ignores unused profit and discount, including NaN
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.8416
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: allocation requires positive sales or an explicitly supplied manual amount
ok 24 - allocation requires positive sales or an explicitly supplied manual amount
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.6866
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: non-finite costs and invalid installments cannot be saved as valid calculations
ok 25 - non-finite costs and invalid installments cannot be saved as valid calculations
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.6531
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: checkout URL follows the configured Mercado Pago environment
ok 26 - checkout URL follows the configured Mercado Pago environment
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.3859
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..26
# tests 26
# suites 0
# pass 26
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 1405.6122
