
> test:security
> npm run test:security:unit


> test:security:unit
> tsx --test tests/*.test.ts

TAP version 13
# Subtest: email selection is literal, normalized and not a wildcard
ok 1 - email selection is literal, normalized and not a wildcard
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.1825
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: ambiguity across pages and lookup failures prevent admin promotion
ok 2 - ambiguity across pages and lookup failures prevent admin promotion
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.1529
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: demo examples keep existing values and calculations reference newly inserted IDs
ok 3 - demo examples keep existing values and calculations reference newly inserted IDs
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.1296
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: creation, demo seed and removal propagate errors without fallback writes or false success
ok 4 - creation, demo seed and removal propagate errors without fallback writes or false success
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.0143
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: license extension retries a conflicting grant instead of losing it
ok 5 - license extension retries a conflicting grant instead of losing it
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.1621
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: license preserves calendar month overflow and trial exact-day arithmetic
ok 6 - license preserves calendar month overflow and trial exact-day arithmetic
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.5786
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: unknown commit outcome is never automatically replayed
ok 7 - unknown commit outcome is never automatically replayed
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.1356
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: conflict retries are bounded and never report false success
ok 8 - conflict retries are bounded and never report false success
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.8305
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: database text item type is validated without inventing an enum
ok 9 - database text item type is validated without inventing an enum
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.8926
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: product stock remains numeric; services persist null in forms, duplication and demo
ok 10 - product stock remains numeric; services persist null in forms, duplication and demo
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.7659
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: Mercado Pago insert explicitly supplies provider and pending state
ok 11 - Mercado Pago insert explicitly supplies provider and pending state
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.5854
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: payment verification refuses another provider, missing charge and amount mismatch
ok 12 - payment verification refuses another provider, missing charge and amount mismatch
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.3919
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: signup is closed for absent, null or disabled configuration; explicit true enables it
ok 13 - signup is closed for absent, null or disabled configuration; explicit true enables it
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.2892
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: trial uses persisted backend expiration, otherwise creation plus 30 days without writes
ok 14 - trial uses persisted backend expiration, otherwise creation plus 30 days without writes
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.5901
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: accepts a valid recent signature with current or previous secret
ok 15 - accepts a valid recent signature with current or previous secret
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.7776
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: rejects an otherwise valid old signature
ok 16 - rejects an otherwise valid old signature
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.4934
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: rejects an invalid signature
ok 17 - rejects an invalid signature
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.4782
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: does not mix sandbox and production payments
ok 18 - does not mix sandbox and production payments
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.2769
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: classifies payment states conservatively
ok 19 - classifies payment states conservatively
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.2819
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: GET, invalid signatures, stale/future timestamps and ambiguous ids never process
ok 20 - GET, invalid signatures, stale/future timestamps and ambiguous ids never process
  ---
  duration_ms: 50.3419
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: valid notifications use only signed id and repeat through the idempotent processor
ok 21 - valid notifications use only signed id and repeat through the idempotent processor
  ---
  duration_ms: 4.3974
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: missing configuration and processor failures produce retryable errors
ok 22 - missing configuration and processor failures produce retryable errors
  ---
  duration_ms: 5.5344
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: disabled or missing payment configuration blocks new charges even with env token
ok 23 - disabled or missing payment configuration blocks new charges even with env token
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.5021
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: existing payments can still be reconciled and active charges use credential fallback
ok 24 - existing payments can still be reconciled and active charges use credential fallback
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.3738
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: promotional discount rejects out-of-range and non-finite values
ok 25 - promotional discount rejects out-of-range and non-finite values
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.6076
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: discount boundaries produce a non-negative price and expose loss
ok 26 - discount boundaries produce a non-negative price and expose loss
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.5281
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: minimum mode ignores unused profit and discount, including NaN
ok 27 - minimum mode ignores unused profit and discount, including NaN
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.7599
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: allocation requires positive sales or an explicitly supplied manual amount
ok 28 - allocation requires positive sales or an explicitly supplied manual amount
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.6325
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: non-finite costs and invalid installments cannot be saved as valid calculations
ok 29 - non-finite costs and invalid installments cannot be saved as valid calculations
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.391
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: checkout URL follows the configured Mercado Pago environment
ok 30 - checkout URL follows the configured Mercado Pago environment
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.1892
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..30
# tests 30
# suites 0
# pass 30
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 1092.9834
